Boxing: n.   拳击
Lesson 21. Daniel Mendoza. Boxing matches were very popular in England 200 years ago.
第21课。丹尼尔·门多萨（Daniel Mendoza）。拳击比赛在200年前在英格兰非常受欢迎。
boxer: n.   拳击手, bare: adj. 赤裸的
In those days, boxers fought with bare fists for prize money. Because of this, they were known as
在那些日子里，拳击手用裸露的拳头为奖金而战。因此，他们被称为
crude: adj. 粗野的
prize fighters. However, boxing was very crude, for these were no rules and a prize fighter could
奖品战士。但是，拳击非常粗糙，因为这不是规则，奖金可以
be seriously injured or even killed during a match. One of the most colorful figures in boxing
在比赛中受到重伤甚至被杀。拳击中最丰富多彩的人物之一
history was Daniel Mendoza. Who was born in 1764? The use of gloves was not introduced until
历史是丹尼尔·门多萨（Daniel Mendoza）。谁出生于1764年？直到
technically: adv. 严格根据法律意义地
1860, when the marquee of Queensborough drew up the first set of rules. Though he was technically a
1860年，当昆斯伯勒的侯爵夫人提出了第一组规则。虽然从技术上讲他是一个
crude: adj. 粗野的, science: n.   科学
prize fighter, Mendoza did much to change crude prize fighting into a sport, for he brought science
门多萨（Mendoza）的奖品战斗机为将粗略的奖品斗争变成一项运动而做了很多，因为他带来了科学
popularity: n.   名望, adore: v.   崇拜，爱戴
to the game. In this day, Mendoza enjoyed tremendous popularity. He was adored by Rich and Porra like
到游戏。在这一天，门多萨享有极大的流行。他被Rich和Porra喜欢
fame: n.   名声
Mendoza rose to fame swiftly after a boxing match when he was only 14 years old.
拳击比赛只有14岁后，门多萨（Mendoza）在拳击比赛后迅速上升。
boxer: n.   拳击手, eminent: adj. 著名的，杰出的
This attracted the attention of Richard Humphreys who was then the most eminent boxer in England.
这吸引了理查德·汉弗莱斯（Richard Humphreys）的注意，他当时是英格兰最杰出的拳击手。
He offered to train Mendoza and his young pupil was quick to learn. In fact, Mendoza soon
他提出要训练门多萨，他的年轻学生很快学习。实际上，门多萨很快
bitterly: adv. 厉害地
became so successful that Humphreys turned against him. The two men quarreled bitterly and it was
变得如此成功，以至于汉弗莱斯反对他。两个人痛苦地吵架了，那是
clear that the argument could only be settled by a fight. A match was held at Stilton, where both
很明显，该论点只能通过战斗来解决。一场比赛在斯蒂尔顿举行了
bet: v.   打赌
men fought for an hour. The public bet a great deal of money on Mendoza. But he was defeated. Mendoza
男人战斗了一个小时。公众在门多萨（Mendoza）押注了很多钱。但是他被击败了。门多萨
met Humphreys in the ring on a later occasion and he lost for a second time. It was not until his
以后在戒指上遇到汉弗莱斯，他第二次输了。直到他
third match in 1790 that he finally beat Humphreys and became champion of. England, meanwhile, he
1790年，他终于击败了汉弗莱斯并成为冠军。同时，英格兰
academy: n.   专业学校
founded a highly successful academy and even Lord Byron became one of his pupils. He earned
建立了一所非常成功的学院，甚至拜伦勋爵也成为了他的学生之一。他赚了
enormous sums of money and was paid as much as $100 for a single appear one of his pupils.
一笔巨额的钱，单人的薪水高达100美元，出现了他的一位学生。
He earned enormous sums of money and was paid as much as $100 for a single appearance.
他赚了巨额资金，单场外观的薪水高达100美元。
boxer: n.   拳击手, extravagant: adj. 浪费的，奢移的
Despite this, he was so extravagant that he was always in debt. After he was defeated by a boxer
尽管如此，他还是如此奢侈，以至于他总是负债累累。在他被拳击手击败之后
called Gentlemen Jackson. He was quickly forgotten. He was sent to prison for failing to pay his debts
称为杰克逊先生。他很快被遗忘了。他因未能偿还债务而被送进监狱
poverty: n.   贫困
and died in poverty in 1836.
并于1836年在贫困中死亡。